Now we're married, aren't we,
Sakamoto?
We are, Himiko.
Only in the world of BTOOOM!, but we are.
Here, all we have are hearts that
believe in each other's humanity.
This may be a true, pure love.
Still...
I want to meet you.
Let's not.
I like it this way.
I want to keep dreaming this way.
I like you this way.
Himiko...
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
If they're farther away in my next scan, we won't have to fight.
Damn it.
What the hell?
He attacked me with a knife, not a BIM?
Don't move!
Why did you attack me?
Don't you think trying to kill each other is stupid?!
Stop this, and work with us.
We'll escape together.
How?
Well...
No plan, huh?
You can't beat a BIM with a knife!
First persuasion, then threats?
I hate selfish kids like you more than anything.
Say what you like.
I'm leaving.
If you try to follow me...
So it was him.
They're working together?
An explosion!
That's where Sakamoto went, isn't it?
I hope he's okay.
He has three types of BIMs.
For all your talk, you're a murderer yourself!
There isn't any point in wasting BIMs on him.
Mr. Miyamoto, stab him with your knife.
If you want, I could—
Damn it! What did you do?!
W-Wait!
The stun gun's getting weaker.
Crap!
That stupid kid...
Mr. Miyamoto, go after him.
I was planning to let him go.
This is what he said to me:
"Work with us."
Virtual Bride
He has friends.
S-Sakamoto!
You took your time.
Are you okay?
I'm fine,
but my BIMs were taken.
You didn't let them follow you, did you?
It's all right.
I took the longest way back I could find.
And they weren't using their radar.
They must have lost track of me by now.
Radar?
No!
They could use footprints or other traces like that!
No, I can't stay here.
I'm leaving.
Give me back my things.
Wait.
There's only one trunk.
Then give it to me.
Listen...
What?
Don't move.
H-How did you find us?!
I used to be a mercenary.
Tracking someone in the jungle is simple for me.
We meet again, little girl.
When I saw his stun gun, I realized...
If I followed him, we might meet again.
Are those the BIMs and the
food you took from me?
I'm taking them back.
Come to think of it, wasn't that fat-ass Akechi with you?
You killed him, didn't you?
Do you have his chip?
I-It wasn't me!
I did nothing wrong!
I don't know where his chip is.
I don't have it!
That's fine.
I'll just strip search you for it.
Stop it!
Leave us alone.
Get out of here!
You still don't understand?
This island is hell. You live or you die.
It's impossible to escape on your own.
The only way out is to kill
others and take their chips.
Don't you want to get eight chips and leave this place?
If you ask me, the people playing the game
are the sane ones.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
No matter what's going on, murder is never justified!
This is a game someone made.
A game this size must have
balancing issues somewhere.
I worked as a debugger for Tyrannos Japan, the guys who are probably running this.
So somehow, I can tell!
This game isn't complete.
It's still being developed.
There's a loophole somewhere!
I know it.
Your plan is nothing but a child's foolish optimism.
I'm not interested.
Die.
Getting that chip is gonna be a pain.
Right, little girl?
Himiko...
H-Himiko...
Ouch.
I fell from up there?!
Th-The others!
Mr. Taira?
S-Sakamoto...
We need to stop the bleeding.
The trunk... and the BIMs!
He took them?
Where's the girl?
Did he take her?
No...
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
BTOOOM!?
A type theta cosplay?
Himiko...
That's her name?
No way. Then she's...
my Himiko?
I have to go...
and save her.
Himiko...
No! Don't go!
Please don't go.
I can't handle any more waiting.
We need clean towels and water for you.
I'll be back soon.
I promise.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
This time, it's over.
If you leave me here, I... I...
I won't be able to stay sane.
Please, stay here!
Sa...
Sakamoto!
That's good stuff.
I feel so much better.
Stop!
That's my food!
You bitch...
It was mine before you stole it.
Just hurry up and kill me.
I won't fight back.
In exchange...
Let me die pure.
Do you think that's why I brought you here?
There are better forms of
entertainment on a battlefield.
Torturing the enemy.
Flaying.
Like peeling the skin off an apple.
Tear off all the skin, and see how long they survive.
I'll make your body pure, just the way you want.
No!
What?
That was radar, wasn't it?
That old guy with the Kansai accent?
Or was it another player?
Don't you dare!
They each fired their radar twice.
Do you think it's some kind of signal?
That means it's probably...
That kid survived.
The squall's passed.
He'll be here soon.
You head to the front hall.
I'll go around from the left.
We took all his BIMs.
He's unarmed, so don't screw up.
Leave it to me.
Your BIMs have a ten-second
delay before they explode.
Set them to three so you don't mess up.
Right!
Okay.
He's heading toward Natsume.
The fool.
I can tell exactly where you are.
Natsume, did you get him?
He's getting closer.
Did Natsume miss?
No, he didn't.
If there isn't another explosion...
Did he get Natsume?
He's heading straight for me.
That means he'll be coming through here.
I'll take him in one strike.
Do you think I can't hear you?
You're mine!
Where is he?
What happened?
I-I saw him, so I attacked.
But he disappeared completely.
Is it possible to completely disintegrate someone so there's nothing left?
Of course not, you fool.
Look harder!
I'm certain she was around here.
That was close.
That was a military-style trap.
But I avoided it!
And I got a valuable BIM.
A BIM that's been disabled becomes
the property of whoever disarmed it.
I proved that with her BIM.
Maybe with this, I can make a miracle happen.
I've come to save you,
Himiko.
H-How do you know that name?
Sorry, I saw your phone wallpaper.
You played BTOOOM! as "Himiko," didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
It isn't my real name, though.
My name is Sakamoto.
Have you ever heard of me?
It's possible we've played together a lot.
I know the name.
If you mean the world-ranked player,
then you were famous among my friends.
But the name is all I know.
We've never played together.
It wasn't you?
I don't play that much.
Of course.
That game sold three million copies.
There was bound to be users sharing the same name.
But I got the courage to come this far because I thought it was Himiko.
So from now on,
I'll just have to believe in my heart.
Even if it's not your real name, can I call you Himiko?
I guess I don't mind.
Thanks.
That bastard's with the girl.
He never showed up on the radar!
He made it through the trap and into the room?
Christ... The radar, the BIMs...
I knew this was the only thing I could trust.
There are only two ways down from that room.
You go this way.
I'll get the side.
Don't screw it up this time.
Right!
Yahoo!
Penal Code Section 361 Article 1, self-defense!
Necessary actions taken in defense of a pressing and illegal threat are not punishable by law!
Self-defense! Self-defense!
I found you!
Die, die, die!
Unarmed fool!
I can't die in this crazy world.
I am an elite lawyer!
Fool!
That leads to a dead end...
Not bad, kid.
I'm impressed.
But I've got the girl.
Come on out.
I'll give you a chance: an unarmed fight.
It's not a bad deal, is it?
Now, come out.
If I can get that...
Your pouch had three BIM types.
You should have at least two chips.
This girl killed that fat-ass Akechi,
so she has one, too.
I said I don't have it!
You're still playing dumb?
That's fine.
You should have three between you.
Once I kill you, I can take my time looking.
Natsume, the guy with the Kansai accent,
and the one I killed before make eight total.
That's all I need.
So get on out here!
If you beat me, you can get all eight, too.
Now.
The knife's the first thing most people go for!
Damn it!
I won't let you die easily.
I said to fight barehanded,
but you ignored me and went for the knife.
That's against the rules.
Is this the end of the line?
Life didn't work out the way I wanted.
I thought it would somehow, but it never did.
A life wasted on games...
If I could have at least met the real Himiko...
What are you doing?
You bitch...
Hurry, run!
What did you...
What?
Run! This way!
She triggered the bomb?
The gas is coming!
Where's the exit?
A dead end?
No way.
What are you going to do?
Wow.
Come on!
Gotcha.
Just a little further.
What?
I-I'll show you hell.
The real hell that I saw on the battlefield.
He's good.
But...
A timer?
Why would he?
It'll be ten seconds until it explodes.
I've got plenty of time.
I'll make it mine and use it...
Set them to three so you don't mess up.
He took Natsume's...
S-Sorry.
Wow!
Wonderful.
It's like a movie.
Sakamoto defeated Miyamoto Masashi, the favorite to win!
What do you think, everyone?
In the third round, the game's balance has really improved!
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
I hold my breath and close my eyes
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
The sky is glittering so brightly
kono machi no zujou wo color
Coloring the space over our heads
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't stop shedding tears
omoide ni wa dekinai
I can't just push it aside as memories
au dake de ureshikatta
Just seeing you made me so happy
kimi no koto shirazu ni
I didn't understand you
kizutsukete
And hurt you
nobody knows
Nobody knows
gomen ne watashi wo mou
You don't have to give me another chance
yurusanaide wasurete
Just forget about me
After Himiko and I just barely fend off the enemy players,
a new threat approaches.
A white ghost that Himiko says she saw in the darkness...
Does it mean there's a new enemy?
Episode
White Ghost
Or is it...